https://www.pazsaz.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
We take your privacy very seriously here at the Pazsaz Entertainent Network. This site does not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:
Log Information: When you access the Pazsaz Entertainment Network, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
User Communications: When you send email or other communications to the Pazsaz Entertainment Network, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. The data you do provide us will be used under the strictest control; we will NOT provide people with your email address without your permission. We loathe use of "SPAM" email and will not sell or provide your email address for such purposes.
Links: The Pazsaz Entertainment Network may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. No other information, other than the the quantity of times a link has been followed, is collected. This website is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the websites found at the link urls.
Advertising: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
On the Internet, all information collected is defined as being either anonymous or personally identifiable:
Anonymous Information: Refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For instance, we may know that ten thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live, or their date of birth. Most of the information we collect about our users is Anonymous Information.
Personally Identifiable Information: Refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are such as your name, email address, or postal address. You voluntarily give some of this information when you enter a contest on our site or submit a link to us. The choice of how much of your personally identifiable information that
you choose to tell us is left completely up to you. Like you, we at the Pazsaz Entertainment Network have children of our own and are concerned about their safety when they use the Internet. We want you and your family to be safe while visiting our Internet site. That is why, consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role to protect the privacy of their children and to prevent inappropriate use of information about their children. Parents and guardians should instruct their children never to give out real names or any other identifying information over the Internet without first getting parental permission. The Pazsaz Entertainment Network will remove any information provided online by children upon the request of the child or the parent or guardian.
How the information we do collect is used:
We monitor the page views of the users as a whole of our site to determine what our users want and do not want.
We develop summary, but not individual, reports for our advertisers. The people that make it possible for you to use the Pazsaz Entertainment Network for free, our advertisers, need this information to determine how effective their advertising investments are. We never tell our advertisers who it was that saw or clicked on their advertisements, in fact we do not know ourselves.
Other companies which place advertising or sell products on our site may collect information about you when you view or click on their advertising or content through the use of cookies. Cookies are small pieces of electronic information which a Web site can store on a visitor's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow Web site operators to "personalize" the site to match your individual preferences. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major Web sites use them. You can choose to set your browser to notify you whenever you are sent a cookie. This gives you the option to decide whether or not to accept a cookie. Due to the way the Internet technically operates, we cannot control this collection of information.
This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.
| Pazsaz Home | Copyright & Disclaimer |
FAQ |
Privacy Policy |
Partners |
Contact Us |
